In this exercise, we'd like you to take what you know about looping and turtles,
在这次演习中我们想让你了解循环和海龟
and draw something of your own.
把你自己的东西画出来
But specifically, we've given you a list of the colors
但具体来说 我们给了你一份颜色列表
of the rainbow and we'd like you to draw something rainbow colored.
我们希望你能画出彩虹色的东西
You can use a loop over this list to draw a shape with different colored sides.
您可以在此列表上使用循环来绘制具有不同颜色边的形状
Here are just a couple of examples of shapes that you can create with a loop like that.
这里有几个形状的例子 你可以用这样的循环创建
You could make a hexagon,
你可以做个六角形
whose sides are just different colors,
他们的肤色不同
or you could take some time and figure out how to
或者你可以花点时间想出办法
draw a rainbow or you could do something totally different.
画出彩虹或者你可以做些完全不同的事
After you try it, we'll show you the code for both of these.
在你尝试之后 我们会向你们展示这两者的代码